NAA Records 5775
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Luskin, Bert L., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  Includes NAA Umpire Volume, Second Draft (7/25/56)The John Deere-UAW Permanent Arbitration System by Harold W. Davey, 41p. and related correspondence
- Luskin, Bert L., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  Includes correspondence about Braden Memorial Fund 6/57; correspondence regarding establishing a group pension or retirement plan 6/57
- Luskin, Bert L., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  Letter from Walter Seinsheimer expressing disappointment that his application was not approved
- Luskin, Bert L., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 64)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 69)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 70)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1961 (Box 16, Folder 71)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1949 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1949 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Includes Membership Committee Report for 1950, 9p.; Routine
- Luskin, Bert L., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Includes final draft of the Code of Ethics and Procedural Standards For Labor-Management Arbitration, 12p.; Routine
- Luskin, Bert L., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Includes speech of Ralph T. Seward on 3/30/51: Arbitration In The World Today, 14p.; Routine
- Luskin, Bert L., 1951 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Includes Act Relating to Arbitration and to Make Uniform the Law With Reference Thereto, 11p.
- Luskin, Bert L., 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Includes - Annual Report of the Secretary for 1957, 5p.; Report of Bert Luskin on the first decade of the NAA; Routine
- Luskin, Bert L., 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Includes Report of the Ethics Committee for 1958, 4p.; Annual Report of the Secretary for 1957; Routine
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Haughton, Ronald W., 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 74)
- Miller, David P., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Miller, David P., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Miller, David P., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Miller, David P., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Miller, David P., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Miller, David P., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Correspondence regarding Self-Employed Individuals Tax Retirement Act of 1962
- Miller, David P., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Miller, David P., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Miller, David P., 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Routine and correspondence regarding Self-Employed Individuals Tax Retirement Act of 1962
- Miller, David P., 1963-1967 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Miller, David P., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Includes proposed H.R.10 plan (Pension)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Miller, David P., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Miller, David P., 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  Includes bibliographies sent to people requesting information for the High School Debate topic of the year on compulsory arbitration
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  letter from Harry Platt objecting to the suggested "guest policy" at annual meetings
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  Correspondence regarding rejection of Walter G. Seinsheimer application; letter from Laurence Seibel outlining his understanding of the Academy's membership policy 4/12/66, 3p.
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Miller, David P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  Includes correspondence from Jacob Seidenberg regarding liaison with federal agencies 4/66; correspondence about what NAA should do in the Civil Rights area and routine
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  Correspondence about refection of Raymond Scheib application and routine
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Miller, David P., 1967 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Miller, David P., 1954-1967 (Box 18, Folder 60a)
  Correspondence regarding Code of Ethics
- Miller, David P., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 62)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 63)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 65)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 66)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 67)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 68)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 69)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 70)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 71)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 72)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 73)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 74)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 75)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 76)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 77)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 78)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 79)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1968-1975 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  Includes forms and correspondence with U.S. Internal Revenue Service about NAA application for tax-exempt status and correspondence about whether NAA qualifies to do business in Pennsylvania
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Includes copy of "Non-Profit Corporations - 1969" annual report to Michigan Department of Treasury; correspondence regarding Rolf Valtin's recommendation that Judge David H. Brown withdraw his application for membership; correspondence regarding "pre-striking" of arbitrators names from panel lists 4/69; insurance policy, general liability in force for the NAA from 1/28/69-2/2/69, and routine
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Includes rejection of application for membership of Robert L. Gibson 11/70, and of Anthony B. Sinicropi 4/70; "Report on Proposed NAA Relationships With Overseas Neutrals" 4pp. 3/12/69, and routine
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  Includes rejection of application for membership of James P. Martin 2/3/71, and routine
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  Includes correspondence regarding the pre-publication of Jean McKelvey's 1971 Presidential Address 4/72, and routine
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 47)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  Signed agreement between the NAA and the Bureau of National Affairs to publish the Proceedings of the 27th annual meeting of the NAA 7/15/74, 5p.
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 51)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 52)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 53)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 54)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 55)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 56)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 57)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 58)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Correspondence about informing Victor L Lleras Delgado of Puerto Rico that he does not meet requirements for membership in NAA 1/76; form letter to all members of the academy about dues waiver policy, dues structure, and conflict within the NAA about its policies and the style and manner of its operations, 12p. n.d.; much related correspondence
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  Copy of Frederic Meyers' proposed amendment to Article V of the By-laws of NAA(regarding dues)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Dybeck, Alfred C., 1971-1976 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  routine
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979-1983 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Includes letter to Julius Draznin rejecting his application for membership and routine
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  Includes memo to Mark Kahn, Chairman of Membership Committee, regarding Bloch's policy for issuing application to prospective candidates 5/24/82. 3p.; Recommendation of Arnold Zack and Tia Schneider Denenberg as candidates for Delegation Leaders to the People to People Citizen Ambassador Program with the Peoples' Republic of China; description of program
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Bloch, Richard I., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Jones, Dallas, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary, 1950-1960 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary, 1968-1971 (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Annual Reports of the Secretary, 1977-1982 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Releases, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Releases, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Releases, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 52)
- Releases, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 53)
- Releases, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Releases, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 55)
- Releases, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Releases, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Releases, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Releases, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Releases, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Releases, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Releases, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Releases, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Releases, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Releases, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Releases, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Releases, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Releases, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Releases, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Releases, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Releases, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Releases, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Releases, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Mailings, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Mailings, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Mailings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Mailings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Mailings, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Mailings, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Mailings, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 31)